This cake is amazing!
這蛋糕太好吃了
My God, get a room.
天啊，你躲一邊吃吧。
I would get a room with this cake.
躲一邊兒幹啥？
I think I could show this cake a good time.
正是時候讓你們看看美味的蛋糕呢。
If you had to, what would you give up, food or sex?
如果你們必須放棄一樣的話 你們會放棄哪一樣兒，食物還是性愛？
Sex.
性愛
Seriously, answer faster.
說真的，你回答得也太快了吧
Oh, I'm sorry, honey.
不好意思，親愛的
But when she said "sex", I wasn't thinking about sex with you.
我剛才說的性愛，並不是指和你一起的性愛
It's like a giant hug.
好像我還受了很大恩惠似的。
Ross, how about you? Which would you give up?
羅斯，你呢？ 你會放棄哪一樣？性愛還是食物？
Food.
食物
How about sex or dinosaurs?
那如果是性愛和恐龍呢？
Oh, my God, it's like Sophie's Choice.
老天啊，就像是「索菲的選擇」
Oh, God.
哦，天啊
What about you, Joe? What would you give up, sex or food?
喬伊，你放棄什麼？性愛還是食物？
I don't know, it's too hard.
我不知道，這太難取捨了
No, you gotta pick one.
不行，你必須得選一個
Food. No, sex.
食物，不，性愛
Food. Sex. Food. Sex.. I don't know! Oh, God, I want both!
食物，性愛，食物，性愛… 我不知道，老天，我都想要！
I want.. I want girls on bread!
我要坐在麵包上的妞兒！
The One Where Chandler Gets Caught
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
-You gotta see these pictures of Emma. -Oh, how cute!
-我這兒有我女兒最新的照片 -哇，真可愛啊
-She looks just like a little doll. -Oh, no, that is a doll.
-她看上去就像個洋娃娃 -不不，那就是個洋娃娃
Oh, thank God, because that thing's really creepy.
噢，感謝上帝，因為我覺得它看上去有點嚇人
Look, there's Chandler.
錢德在那兒
Who's the blond? She's pretty.
噢，那個金髮女郎是誰？她很漂亮
He's having an affair.
他有外遇了
He is not having an affair!
他才不是有外遇呢
I'm always right about these things.
你知道的啦，我在這事兒上面感覺很準的。
No, you're not. Last week, you thought Ross was trying to kill you.
不，你才沒有呢 上周你還在想羅斯想把你宰了
Well, sorry, but it's hard to believe that anyone would tell a story that dull..
對不起，但確實很讓人難以相信 有人能講一個洋娃娃...
just to tell it.
也會講的故事。
There's something going on with them.
我敢發誓他們倆之間肯定有些什麼事
Look! He's getting into the car with her.
快看，他們倆上了同一部車
That doesn't mean anything.
那並不能說明什麼
Oh, yeah? Well, let's see.
是嗎？讓我們走著瞧
Okay, duck down.
喂, 趴低點
-Hello? -Hi, Chandler. It's Phoebe.
-喂? -嗨，錢德，我是菲比
I know that Monica is working today..
我知道今天莫尼卡要上班
so I was wondering if you wanted to come to the movies with me and Rachel.
所以我想你要不要跟我和瑞秋一起去看電影
Oh, I have to work too. Yeah, I'm stuck here at the office all day.
噢，我也得上班。 我在這辦公室裡都悶了有一天了
Well, it's a shame that you'll miss the movie..
太可惜了，你不能去看電影
because we were gonna see, you know, either Liar Liar..
因為我們打算看《騙子，騙子》
or Betrayal or An Affair to Remember.
《背叛》或者是《不了情》
Those are all really old.
噢，這些片子很新啊
Okay, then maybe it'll be..
是啊，也可能會看。。。
Dude, Where's My Car?
老兄，我的車呢?
-What? -They're in a car.
-什麼？ -他們現在在車裡
Okay. Well, talk to you later, okay? Bye.
好了，遲點再跟你說，再見
Jeez!
Okay, quick. We gotta find a cab and follow them.
快，我們得攔輛的士跟蹤他們
Yeah, okay. Let me just grab my night-vision goggles and my stun gun.
好的，我得先去拿我的夜視鏡和眩暈槍
I got them.
我這兒有
-Hey. -Hey. Hi, sweetie.
-嘿 -嗨，親愛的
Hey, you smell like perfume and cigarettes.
你身上有香水和香煙的味道
-I was in the car with Nancy. -Nancy doesn't smoke.
-我今天和南茜在車裡面呆了一天 -南茜可不抽煙
Well, at least the perfume's not mine. Be thankful for that.
那至少那香水不是我的 你這點倒是不用擔心。
So.. What did you think of the house?
那麼，你認為那房子怎麼樣？
It's everything we've been looking for.
簡直太棒了，就是我們一直以來要找的
Isn't it? And what about the amazing wanes coating..
是嗎？那些漂亮的塗層，冠形屋頂
the crown molding and the dormer windows in the attic?
偏廈窗子和閣樓？
And the wiggle woms and the zip zorps!
還有蠕蟲和爬蟲？
What were the things you said?
你剛剛在說什麼？
-Don't you love the huge yard? -The fireplace in the bedroom.
-你喜歡那個大院子嗎？ -還有睡房裡的壁爐
And Nancy said it's really underpriced..
南茜還說這個價錢非常優惠
because the guy lost his job and has to move in with his parents!
因為那傢伙丟了工作不得不搬去跟父母住 所以急於出手。
This is bringing out a lovely color in you.
看把你興奮的
So do you think we should get it?
你認為我們是不是應該把它買下來？
I don't know. What do you think?
我不知道，你怎麼想？
-I think we should. -I do too.
-我想我們應該買下來 -我也這麼想
This is huge. How bad do you wanna smoke right now?
這是很大件事。 現在想不想抽一支？
I don't know what you mean, giant, talking cigarette.
你說什麼呢，進言有功獎勵香煙？
Phoebe called as I was getting into Nancy's car.
對了，我正在南茜車上的時候，菲比打電話來了
If she asks you, I was at work all day.
如果她問起就說我一天都在工作
Got you. When do we tell them?
明白，你打算什麼時候跟他們說這件事
We don't. Not until it's 100 percent. Why upset everybody over nothing?
至少要等到事情完全確定下來，我是說 八字還沒一撇，沒有必要讓大家都難受
Okay. Right.
嗯，好的
-Oh, my God, that is gonna be so hard. -I know. Good luck with it.
-上帝，這將會非常難受 -我知道。一切順利吧
I just can't see Chandler cheating.
我只是不明白錢德為什麼要騙莫尼卡
I'm telling you guys, we followed them out to a house in Westchester.
告訴你們吧，我們一直跟蹤他們 到一所位於西切斯特的房子的外面
They went in for 45 minutes, and then they came out looking pretty happy.
他們在裡面待了有45分鐘， 出來的時候兩人看上去都很高興
Chandler?
錢德？
Forty-five minutes?
45分鐘？
Well, something's not right.
肯定有什麼地方不對頭
So you went all the way to Westchester, waited 45 minutes..
所以你們跟蹤到 西切斯特  還在外面等了45分鐘
-and came back in a cab? -Yeah.
-然後坐出租車回來？ -是啊
If each of you guys would like to pitch in 100 bucks, that would be great.
如果你們誰願意扔個100大元進去 那真是太好了
I can't believe he'd do this to Monica.
我不敢相信他這樣對莫尼卡
I know, and with the baby coming?
是啊，而且他們就快有小孩了
-So should we tell her? -I don't know.
-那我們該不該告訴莫尼卡？ -我不知道
If one of us saw Mike with another woman, would you want us to tell you?
菲比，如果我們看到麥克跟另一個女人在一起， 我們應不應該告訴你？
Why? Who'd you see him with?
什麼？你看到他跟誰在一起了？
-No one. I'm just saying if we did.. -Tell me what you know!
-沒有，我只是說 -告訴我你知道些什麼！
No one! Nothing! Mike's a great guy! It was hypothetical!
我什麼也不知道，我只是假設
All right. He is a good guy.
好了，好了，他是個好人
You're right. He wouldn't cheat.
是啊，他是個好人，他不會騙我的
If I did see him with someone, there's no way I..
如果我真看到他跟另一個女人在一起。。。
Who did you see him with?
你看見他跟誰在一起了？
Oh, look at her. So happy.
看，她多開心啊
If only there were a smaller one to clean this one.
要是有更小的來清理這個該有多好
Hey, is Chandler here?
錢德在嗎？
No, he's picking up dinner. Why? What's up?
不在，他去買晚餐去了，出什麼事了嗎？
Look, whatever happens, we're here for you, and we love you.
無論發生什麼事， 我們都跟你在一起，我們愛你
-All right. -We think Chandler might be having an affair.
-好 -我想錢德可能有外遇了
-What? -Phoebe and I saw Chandler..
-什麼？ -菲比和我今天
with a blond woman today outside on the street.
看見錢德和一個金髮女郎在一起
And then we followed them to a house in Westchester.
然後我們跟蹤他們到了 一所位於西切斯特的房子
They went in together. I'm so sorry.
他們一起進去了，很抱歉
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, that's awful.
我的上帝。。。 太可怕了。
What did you think of the house?
你覺得房子怎麼樣?
What?
什麼？
Monica, you understand what we're saying, right?
莫尼卡 你明白我剛才說的話 對不對？
Yeah. Sure. I mean, I'm devastated, obviously.
明白，當然明白 非常清楚你的意思
Did you think the neighborhood was homey?
你們認為那些鄰居熱不熱情？
-Hey. -You son of a bitch.
-嘿！ -你這個狗雜種
Is it me, or have the greetings gone downhill around here?
你是在說我還是說 那個在這附近遊蕩的進過局子的毒販？
Phoebe and Rachel saw you with Nancy today.
菲比和瑞秋今天看見你和南茜在一起
They think you're having an affair.
他們以為你和她有一腿
-Who's Nancy? -What's going on?
-誰是南茜？ -到底是怎麼回事？
Okay..
好的。。。
All right, you better sit down.
好的，好的，夥計們，坐下說話
-This is.. This is pretty big. -Yeah.
-這是件大事 -是的
I'm not having an affair.
我沒有外遇
Nancy is our realtor.
南茜是我們的房地產經紀
I knew he couldn't be with a woman for 45 minutes!
我就知道他不可能跟一個女人做45分鐘那麼長
Why do you have a realtor?
你們為什麼要請地產經紀？
She's been showing us houses outside of the city.
最近以來她帶著我們去看市區以外的房子
-What? -Are you serious?
-什麼？ -你是說真的？
When we found out that we were gonna get this baby..
我們認為因為我們馬上就要有小孩了
Chandler and I decided we didn't want to raise a kid in the city.
我和錢德決定 我們不能在市區撫養我們的小孩
So you're.. So you're gonna move?
所以你們要搬出去？
Oh, my God.
我的上帝！
Shouldn't we all vote on stuff like this?
這種事我們總要投票解決吧？
What is wrong with raising a kid in the city?
在市區裡帶小孩有什麼不妥嗎？
I'm doing it. Ross is doing it.
我不就正在市區裡帶小孩嗎？ 羅斯也是
Sarah Jessica Parker is doing it!
莎拉.傑西卡.派克也是這麼幹的
And that's great for you guys, but we want a lawn and a swing set.
對你們來說這沒什麼問題 但是我們想要一個長長的鞦韆
A street where our kids can ride their bikes..
還有一條小孩可以在上面騎單車的馬路
and maybe an ice-cream truck can go by.
不時還會有雪糕車經過
So you want to buy a house in the '50s.
所以你們想買一棟50年代的房子？
Have you thought about what you're giving up?
你們有沒有想過你們正放棄什麼麼？
You can't move out of the city. What if..?
你們不能搬出市區
What if you want Chinese food at 5 a.m.?
要是，要是你們想凌晨五點鐘吃中餐怎麼辦？
Or a fake Rolex that breaks as soon as it rains?
又或者想買一塊一響就散架的假勞力士怎麼辦？
Or an Asian hooker sent right to your door?
又或者是想電召一個亞洲妓女怎麼辦？
You know what? If you want to look for a house, that's okay.
知道嗎？ 如果你們只是想看看房子，沒問題
No! No, it's not! Don't listen to him. I'm gonna thump you.
不，不， 不，別聽他的 小心我扁你
It's okay, because they have to get it out of their system.
的確是沒問題，但等你們真正住進去之後
Okay? But you're gonna realize this is the only place you want to be.
你們會發現這裡才是你們真正想要住的地方
Actually..
實際上
we already found a house we love.
我們已經找到合我們心意的房子了
-What? -About an hour ago, we made an offer.
-什麼？ -大約一小時以前，我們開出了我們的價碼
Bet you wish I was having an affair now, huh?
我打賭你們現在寧可我有外遇
-You put an offer on a house? -It's so sweet.
-你們已經開出價碼了？ -那房子真的很好
It really is. It has this big yard that leads down to this stream.
的確是，那裡有一個很大的院子 一直通到一條小溪
And then there's these old maple trees.
那裡還有很多楓樹
Oh, again with the nature. What are you, beavers?
跟自然環境有什麼關係？ 你們又不是水獺
Look, I know this is really hard, and we're really sorry.
我知道你們一時很難接受我們的決定， 我們也非常的抱歉
Is this because I come over here without knocking and eat your food?
是不是因為我常常不敲門 就過來拿你們的東西吃?
Because I can stop doing that.
我可以不那樣做
I really, really think I can.
我真的可以改
You know that's not the reason, Joe.
喬伊, 你知道這不是我們要搬出去住的原因
I think if you saw it, you'd understand.
我想如果你們到實地看一看的話 你們會明白的
You guys were there. It's beautiful, isn't it?
你們倆去看過，那的確很美，不是嗎？
-Yeah, it is. -What the hell are you doing?
-是，確實是很美 -你在幹什麼？
Well, it is, all right? When we were out there today, all I kept thinking was:
我的意思是我們今天到那兒的時候 我所想的是
"I can't believe Chandler's screwing this woman..
我簡直不敢相信錢德在和那女人幹那事兒，
but, man, this would be a nice place to live!"
但那並不意味那裡不是一個適合居住的地方！
Yeah, but so is this.
是，但漂亮又能怎樣？
Yeah. I mean, if you move there, you have to leave here.
對，我是說如果你們搬到那裡去住 你們就得離開這兒了
I mean, how can you leave this place?
你們怎麼能離開這個地方？
Come on, Daddy, listen!
爸，你聽我說
All my life, everyone's always told me, "You're a shoe!"
這就好像是我生命的全部 每個人總是對我說 "你是鞋子！"
"You're a shoe! You're a shoe. You're a shoe!"
你是鞋子！你是鞋子，你是鞋子！
I stopped and said, "What if I don't want to be a shoe?
今天我停下來說 如果我不想當鞋子會怎樣？
What if I want to be a purse?
如果我想做手袋？
Or a hat?"
或是帽子？
I don't want you to buy me a hat, I..
不，我不是要你給我買頂帽子
It's a metaphor, Daddy!
我是說我是…啊…我只是打個比方，爸！
You can see where he'd have trouble.
你知道他的麻煩在哪裡了
Well, maybe I'll just stay here with Monica.
好吧，也許我應該和莫尼卡待在這兒
I guess we've established she's staying with Monica.
我猜她的意思是，我們已經就 誰和莫尼卡住在一起這個問題達成了共識
Your money's mine, Greene.
你的錢要歸我啦，格林小姐。
Your fly's open, Geller.
你的尿門沒拉上，蓋勒先生。
You know what I just realized?
夥計們，知道我剛發現了什麼嗎？
"Joker" is "poker" with a "J"!
Joker是帶"J"的Poker
Coincidence?
巧合吧？
That's "joincidence" with a "C"!
嗯，那是帶"C"的'joincidence'
Look! Ugly Naked Guy lit a bunch of candles.
呃，看，那個奇醜的裸男點了一堆蠟燭
That had to hurt!
那太痛苦了
Hey, it's your Thanksgiving too.
嗨，這也是你們的感恩節
Instead of watching football, you could help.
除了看球賽，你也可以過來幫我們幹點活
We know.
我們會的
Rachel, you want to put the marshmallows in concentric circles.
好了，瑞秋， 你想把這些軟糖粒擺成一個同心圓
No, Mon. You want to put them in concentric circles.
不，莫尼卡， 是你想把它們擺成那樣
I want to do this.
我只是想這樣
Every year.
每年如是
It's stuck!
我被卡住了！
Step.
別著急，小心階梯
How did it get on?
你怎麼會把頭給套進去了？
I put it on to scare Chandler.
我想把它戴上去嚇嚇錢德
Oh, my God! Monica's going to totally freak out!
我的上帝，莫尼卡會被嚇死的
Plus, it smells really bad in here.
還有，這裡面難聞得要命
Of course it smells bad. You have your head up a turkey's ass.
那是當然了 你腦袋伸到火雞的屁股裡面去了
Monica.
莫尼卡
Did you get the turkey..?
嗨，你們把火雞塗上油沒有？
Oh, my God!
啊，我的上帝，我的上帝
Who is that?
這是誰？
It's Joey.
是喬伊
I got it!
我明白了。
If we win, they have to get rid of the rooster.
如果我們贏，你們就得把那公雞拿走
That's interesting!
這主意怎麼樣？
If you win..
如果你們贏。。
we give up the bird.
我們就放棄那隻鳥兒
But if we win..
但是，如果我們贏了
we get your apartment.
我們要你們住的地方
-Deal! -What?
-一言為定！ -什麼？
"Monica's nickname when she was a hockey goalie?"
莫妮卡當曲棍球守門員時候的綽號
-Big Fat Goalie. -Correct!
-大胖守門員 -正確。
"Rachel claims it's her favorite movie."
瑞秋說她最喜歡的電影是？
Dangerous Liaisons.
孽戀焚情
-"Her actual favorite movie is..?" -Weekend at Bernie's.
-正確。實際上她最喜歡的電影是？ -老闆渡假去
"Monica categorizes her towels. How many categories are there?"
莫妮卡給她的毛巾分類， 一共分了多少類？
-Everyday use. -Fancy.
-每天用的 -正確
-Guest. -Fancy guest.
-客人的 -正確
-Two seconds. -Eleven?
-2秒 -11種？
Unbelievable! Eleven is correct.
太另人難以置信了，11是正確答案
"Chandler was how old when he first touched a girl's breast?"
錢德第一次摸女孩子胸部的時候有多大？
-14? -No,19.
-14? -不, 19.
Thanks, man.
謝了兄弟
"Joey had an imaginary childhood friend.
喬伊有一個想像中的童年時的朋友
-His name was..?" -Maurice!
-他叫什麼名字？ -莫裡斯
-"His profession was..?" -Space cowboy!
-正確，他是幹什麼的？ -太空牛仔！
"What is Chandler Bing's job?"
錢德是幹什麼工作的？
Ten seconds. You need this or you lose.
還有10秒，你們得答對這一題，否則就輸了
Something to do with transponding.
嗯，好像是跟傳送有關的
He's a transponster!
啊，啊，是搬運工！
That's not even a word!
你說的都不是一個正確的單詞！
You are mean boys who are just being mean!
你們是些卑鄙的傢伙，太卑鄙了!
Don't get mad! No one forced you to raise the stakes.
嗨，別衝我們發火！沒人逼你越賭越大
That is not true! She forced me!
不對，是她逼我的！
You got the question wrong.
是你答錯題了。
It was a stupid, unfair question!
那是一個愚蠢的，不公平的問題。
Don't blame the questions!
願賭服輸，不要把責任怪在問題上
Stop yelling in our apartment! You are ruining moving day for us.
你們能不能不要在屋子裡瞎嚷嚷 你們把我們的搬家日給毀了
Chandler!
錢德！
I saw what you were doing in the window!
錢德，我從窗戶那裡瞧見你們在幹那事兒了
I saw what you're doing to my sister! Get out here!
我看見你在對我妹子做什麼！ 現在你給我滾出去！
Listen, we had a good run.
哇！聽著，我們很恩愛
What was it? Four, five months?
什麼？ 四個月？五個月？
That's more than most people have in a lifetime. Goodbye.
我的意思是 這已經超過大多數人一輩子的恩愛時光了
Hey, Ross. What's up, bro?
嘿，羅斯，出什麼事了，老哥？
What the hell are you doing?
你們到底在幹什麼？！
What's going on?
嘿！出什麼事了？
I think Ross knows about me and Monica.
我想，我想羅斯知道我和莫尼卡的事了
Dude, he's right there.
老兄, 他在那呢
I thought you were my best friend! This is my sister!
我還當你是我最好的朋友呢！她可是我妹妹！
My best friend and my sister! I cannot believe this!
我最好的朋友跟我妹妹！我簡直不敢相信！
We're not just messing around. I love her.
我們不是玩玩而已的。 我愛她
I'm in love with her.
我跟她墜入情網了
I'm so sorry that you had to find out this way.
真不好意思，你是以這種方式知道我們相戀的
I'm sorry, but it's true. I love him too.
抱歉，但這是真的，我也愛他
My best friend and my sister!
我最好的朋友和我妹妹！
I cannot believe this!
我簡直不敢相信！
This is the last box of your clothes.
這是你最後一箱衣服
I'm just gonna label it "What were you thinking?"
我想在這上面貼個標籤，上書：你在想什麼？
I was gonna go across the hall and write that on Chandler.
有趣，因為我正想到對門去 在錢德身上也寫上這句話
Guys, I don't wanna make things worse, but..
二位，我不想把事情搞砸
I don't want to live with Rachel anymore.
但是，嗯，我再也不想跟瑞秋住在一起了
You're so mean to each other.
你們對對方太刻薄了！
I don't wanna end up like that with Rachel. I still like you.
而且我也不想跟瑞秋最後鬧得不歡而散 我還是喜歡你
That's fine because I'm not moving.
菲比，那沒關係，因為我不搬了
Phoebe, you gotta take her.
哇，哇，哇，菲比，你得跟她一起住！
I said some bad stuff..
你知道，我是曾說過一些她的壞話
but Rachel has qualities that make her a good roommate.
但是，瑞秋還是有很多優點的， 這足以讓她成為一個好的室友
She gets tons of catalogs and folds down the pages of things I'd like.
她有很多商品目錄，嗯 她會把那些 她認為我會喜歡的產品所在頁折起來
What else?
還有呢？
When I take a shower..
我在沖涼的時候...
she leaves me notes on the mirror.
她會在鏡子上給我留下留言
I do. I do do that.
是，那是我幹的
That's nice. I like having things to read in the bathroom.
很好，我喜歡在洗手間裡讀點東西
When I fall asleep on the couch..
當我看完書在沙發上睡著的時候，
she covers me with a blanket.
她會為我蓋上一條毯子
Well, you know, I don't want you to be cold.
你知道啦，我不想讓你著涼了
And when I told her that I was gonna move in with Chandler..
還有，當我告訴她 我要搬過去跟錢德一起住的時候，
she was really supportive.
她真的是很支持我
You were so great.
你太好了
You made it so easy.
你把一件困難的事情變得輕鬆簡單
And now you have to leave.
現在，你得走了
And I have to live with a boy!
而我得和一個男生住在一起！
-She really left. -I know.
-她真的走了 -我知道
-Thank you. -No problem, roomie.
-謝謝 -沒問題，室友
-Can I ask you a question? -Sure.
-我能問你一個問題嗎？ -當然！
What the hell is that dog doing here?
那隻狗倒底在那兒幹什麼？
A little toast here. Ding, ding!
我來說點祝酒詞吧
This isn't exactly the kind of Thanksgiving you planned..
我知道這並不是你們所計劃的感恩節
but for me this has been really great.
但對於我來說，這個節真的是太棒了
I think because it didn't involve divorce..
知道嗎？我之所以這樣認為是因為 這個節裡面沒有離婚...
or projectile vomiting.
和吐得一塌糊塗
If you had gone to Vail..
無論怎樣，我只是在想，如果你們去了Vail
or if you had been with your family, or if you didn't have..
如果你們和你們的家人在一起
syphilis and stuff..
如果你沒做性病這類的廣告
we wouldn't be all together.
我們就不可能在一起，對不對？
So I guess what I'm trying to say is..
所以，我想我想說的是
that I'm very thankful that all of your Thanksgivings sucked.
我很感激你們 因為你們的感恩節計劃全砸了
-That's so sweet! -Thank you.
-太感人了 -謝謝
Here's to a lousy Christmas!
為糟糕的聖誕節乾杯
And a crappy New Year!
也為糟糕的新年乾杯
-Hear, hear! -Hear, hear!
-聽著聽著！ -聽著聽著！
You can't move. You just.. You just can't.
你們不能搬，你們就是不能這樣做
Rachel's right. This is where you guys belong.
瑞秋說得對，你們倆是屬於這裡的
You don't wanna live in Westchester. That's the worst of the Chesters.
是啊，你們可不能搬到西切斯特， 聽起來就像"死"切斯特。
You know, sometimes when I'm alone in my apartment, I look over here..
知道嗎，有時我獨自一人在我的寓所的時候 望向這邊
and you guys are just having dinner..
你們正在吃晚餐
or watching TV or something..
看電視或是做著其它什麼事
but it makes me feel better.
這讓我感覺好很多
And now when I look over, who am I gonna see?
現在，你們搬走之後 我再望過來的時候，我會看到誰？
The Gottliebs? The Yangs?
張三？李四？
They don't make me feel so good.
他們不會讓我感覺如此之好！
Yeah. So don't move, okay? Just stay here..
是啊，所以別搬了 對，就留下吧
-and maybe close your blinds at night. -Hey.
-晚上的時候別忘了拉窗簾就行了。 -喂！
Hello?
喂?
It's Nancy. They responded to our offer.
是南茜，他們答覆我們開出的價碼了
And?
然後？
Okay. Thanks.
好的，謝謝
They passed.
他們對我們的出價沒興趣
They said they won't go a penny under the asking price.
他們一個子兒也不願少
-We can't afford that. -I know.
-我們負擔不起那價格 -我知道
Well, there you go.
好了，如你們所願了
I'm really sorry, you guys.
真抱歉
Yeah, I'm sorry too. I'm even more sorry that phone call didn't come..
我也很抱歉。要是那個電話
before I told you about looking through the window.
在我說出從 窗戶那邊望過來之前打來的話，就好了。
Yeah. Well, we're gonna let you be alone.
我們還是讓你們倆單獨待一會兒吧
-You gonna be okay? -Yeah, we'll be okay.
-你們沒事吧？ -我們沒事的
Love you guys.
我愛你們
You know, I'm really sorry I wasn't more supportive before.
很抱歉，剛才沒有支持你們
That's okay. We understand.
沒關係，我們能理解
Yeah, and about this Nancy..
對了，關於這個南茜
If you're not sleeping with her, should I?
如果你沒跟她上床的話，能不能讓我上？
I know there'll be other houses, but I just..
我知道外面還有很多房子，但是這棟。。。
-I love that one so much. -Yeah.
-我太愛這棟房子了 -是啊
Well, it's a good thing we got it then.
所以得到這棟房子是天大的喜事
-What? -We got the house.
-什麼？ -我們買到那房子了
-Oh, my God. -I didn't wanna tell you in front of them.
-噢，我的上帝 -我只是不想當著他們的面告訴你
We got it?! We got the house?!
我們買到那棟房子了
We're getting a house!
-We're getting a house. -And a baby.
-對，我們買到了 -還有小孩
We're growing up.
我們長大了
We sure are.
是啊。
-Who's gonna tell them? -Not it!
-誰去跟他們說呢？ -不是我
Not it! Damn it!
也不是我
Rachel, this is yours.
瑞秋，這是給你的
Why? What are these for?
為什麼送我們這些禮物？
-You'll see. -All right, everybody open them.
-過會你就知道了 -好了，大家都請打開來看看吧
Wow, this is so beautiful!
好漂亮啊
These are the ones I was looking at in the store!
這個正是我上次在商店裡相中的那一款小飾品！
-I know. -Oh, I love this!
-我知道 -我喜歡這個
A meatball sub!
喔，一個肉丸包！
Thanks!
謝謝
Seriously, guys, what's going on? What are these for?
說真的，你們怎麼了？ 為什麼送我們這些禮物？
Well, I didn't know how to tell you before, but...
我先前不知道該怎麼跟你們說, 但是...
-We got the house. -Enjoy!
-我們買到那房子了 -各位好好享受吧
What did they say?
他們剛才說什麼？